A Guide to the Lois Davidson Gottlieb Architectural Collection, 1945-2003
Special Collections, Virginia Polytechnic Institute and State University
Special Collections, Virginia Polytechnic Institute and State University
Lois Davidson Gottlieb Architectural Collection, 1945-2003
Special Collections, Virginia Polytechnic Institute and State University, Blacksburg, Va.
Ms1997-003
7.2 cu. ft. 11 boxes; 13 oversize folders
Papers of Lois Davidson Gottlieb, architectural designer, author, and lecturer. Includes photographs, writings, storyboards, and printed material relating to her various professional activities as an author and lecturer, as well as some drawings from her work as an undergraduate and graduate student. Also includes files and drawings relating to her work on various residential design projects dating from 1951 to 2002.
Gottlieb, Lois Davidson
Administrative Information
Access Restrictions
Collection is open to research.
Acquisition Information
The Lois Davidson Gottlieb Architectural Collection was donated to the International Archive of Women in Architecture by the creator in April 1997. Additional materials were donated in February and March 2003.
Alternative Form Available
The VT Imagebase contains digital images of the exhibit of Gottlieb's work at Virginia Tech in 1998 and images of the Mark Gottlieb residence.
Biographical Information
Lois Davidson Gottlieb (1926-2018) was a residential designer based in San Francisco, California. She was born on November 13,1926 in San Francisco and attended Stanford University from 1944 to 1947, where she studied art and engineering and earned a Bachelor of Arts degree. She served as an apprentice to famed architect Frank Lloyd Wright from 1948 to 1949 as part of the Taliesin Fellowship in Spring Green, Wisconsin and Scottsdale, Arizona. And she did her graduate work at Harvard University's School of Design from 1949 to 1950.
Gottlieb began her career working as a designer for Warren Callister in San Francisco. Her first solo project was the design of the Val Goeschen house, a one-room unit with 576 square feet, in Inverness, CA. She went on to design other residences in Marin County as part of the design team Duncombe-Davidson based in Sausalito, CA. This partnership spanned the years 1951 to 1956. From 1956 to 2002, Gottlieb worked as a freelance residential designer on over 100 projects in the Bay Area and in Riverside, CA, as well as in Washington, Idaho, and Virginia.
Gottlieb served as a lecturer at the College of the Holy Names in Oakland, CA from 1960 to 1964, at Alameda State College in Hayward, CA from 1962 to 1964, and at the University of California Extension in Riverside, CA from 1966 to 1972. She also gave guest lectures at various universities around the world, including one at Virginia Tech in 1996.
Gottlieb's work has been written about in many newspapers and periodicals, including House Beautiful and the Marin County Independent Journal. She has also published several works of her own, including Environment and Design in Housing (a book which was based on her lectures for a course of the same name and was published in 1966) and A Way of Life: An Apprenticeship with Frank Lloyd Wright (which was based on the traveling exhibit of her photographs of Taliesin). Gottlieb's work has also been exhibited in institutions across the country, including a one-woman architectural exhibit at Virginia Tech in 1998 and the exhibit of photographs of Taliesin in2000-2001.
From 1995 to 1996, Gottlieb designed and supervised the construction of an 11,000 sq. ft. home and office complex for her son, Mark Gottlieb, and his family in Fairfax Station, Virginia. She also produced a video, "Building a Dream: A Family Affair," which documents her work on the project.
Scope and Content
The collection consists of files and drawings that relate to Gottlieb's work as an architectural designer of residences in California, Washington, Idaho, and Virginia spanning the time period from 1951 to 2002. The collection also consists of writings, photographs, correspondence, and printed material that relate to Gottlieb's work as an author and lecturer, as well as material relating to her various publications and exhibits and to the documentary video made about her work on 'The Gottlieb House' in Fairfax Station, Virginia. The collection also consists of some work from her days as an undergraduate student at Stanford University and as a graduate student in architecture at Harvard University.
Arrangement
The collection is divided into two series: Professional Papers and Project Records with all files arranged alphabetically.
Index Terms
Persons:
Gottlieb, Lois Davidson, 1926-2018; Wright, Frank Lloyd, 1867-1959
Subjects:
Architectural drawing--20th century.
Genre and Form Terms:
Architectural drawings.
Occupations:
Architects.
Local Subjects:
International Archive of Women in Architecture (IAWA)
Contents List
- Personal and Professional Papers, 1945-2003, undated
  - Biographical Material.
    - Resume. (Box-folder 1-1a)
  - Correspondence, 1974-1975, 1995-2003
    Scope and Contents note
    This subseries primarily consists of correspondence with Milka Bliznakov, Professor Emerita of the College of Architecture and Urban Studies at Virginia Tech and founder of the IAWA, as well as some correspondence relating to courses and other general correspondence.
    - Correspondence, 1997. (Box-folder 3-3)
    - Correspondence related to courses, 1974-1975. (Box-folder 3-1)
    - Correspondence to Milka Bliznakov, 1995-2003. (Box-folder 3-2)
  - Courses and Lectures, 1959-1975, 1996, undated
    This subseries includes outlines, plans, and notes for course "Environment and Design in Housing" given at Alameda State College and The College of the Holy Names in Oakland, CA during the early 1960s, schedules, correspondence, and student comments and writings relating to various lectures and courses given through the Los Angeles City School Districts Adult Education program and through University of California Extension, Riverside during the time period from 1970-1975, and a videotape of a lecture given at Virginia Tech in 1996.
    - Adult Education and Extension programs, Schedules and other material, 1966-1975. (Box-folder 1-14)
    - Course material, "Environment and Design in Housing," 1962. (Box-folder 1-13)
    - Madison Wisconsin lecture, 2002, notes and reference material. (Box-folder 1-17)
    - Notes and reference material, 1959-[1974], undated. (Box-folder 1-12)
    - Student comments and writings, "Environment and Design in Housing," 1973-1974. (Box-folder 1-15)
    - Video of lecture given by Gottlieb at Virginia Tech, 1996. (Box-folder 1-16)
  - Environment and Design in Housing and other writings, 1962-1964, 1972.
    This subseries includes a typed manuscript of Gottlieb's book, Environment and Design in Housing, which was based on the courses she gave at the College of the Holy Names and Alameda State College and which was published by Macmillan Company in 1965, photographs with captions and drawings, which were used as illustrations in the book, as well as some correspondence from the publisher and reference material. The subseries also includes a manuscript of an article written by Gottlieb called "The Balance Between Diversity and Specialization in American and Indian Education."
    - [Drawings, Environment and Design in Housing, 1964]. (Box-folder 2-9)
    - [Drawings, Environment and Design in Housing, 1964]. (Box 8)
    - Manuscript, Environment and Design in Housing, Part I and II, [1964]. (Box-folder 2-2)
    - Manuscript, Environment and Design in Housing, Part III and IV, [1964]. (Box-folder 2-3)
    - Manuscript, Environment and Design in Housing, Part V, 1964. (Box-folder 2-4)
    - Manuscript, Environment and Design in Housing, Part VI and VII, [1964]. (Box-folder 2-5)
    - Manuscript, Environment and Design in Housing, Photographs and captions, [1964]. (Box-folder 2-6,7,8)
    - Manuscript, "The Balance Between Diversity and Specialization in American and Indian Education," [1972]. (Box-folder 2-10)
    - Photographs, Environment and Design in Housing, [1964]. (Box 6,7)
    - Reference material, 1962-1963. (Box-folder 2-1)
  - Exhibits, Publications, and Video Production, 1989-2002.
    This subseries includes transcripts of various interviews pertaining to Gottlieb's experiences during her internship with Frank Lloyd Wright at Taliesin, various material relating to Gottlieb's photographic exhibit, "A Way of Life," which documents her time at Taliesin, a copy of the publication based upon the exhibit, and photographs and other material relating to an exhibit on Gottlieb, titled "Lois Gottlieb: Continuing the Legacy of Frank Lloyd Wright," at Virginia Tech in the spring of 1998. The subseries also includes storyboards for the video ("Building a Dream: A Family Affair") Gottlieb produced about the her work designing and constructing a house in Fairfax Station, VA for her son and a copy of the publication "Architectural Drawings of Lois Davidson Gottlieb, Vol. IX, 1997-2002."
    - Architectural Drawings of Lois Davidson Gottlieb, Vol. IX, 1997-2002. (Box 8)
    - A Way of Life by Lois Davidson Gottlieb and Eva Soltes, undated (Box 8)
    - "A Way of Life," Exhibition material, 1999. (Box-folder 3-8)
    - "Building a Dream: A Family Affair," Storyboard, 1997, 2002. (Box-folder 3-6)
    - "Building a Dream: A Family Affair," Storyboard, 1997. (Box 8)
    - "Building A Dream: A Family Affair," correspondence. (Box-folder 3-16)
    - Documentary Footage (4 betacam tapes). (Box 9)
    - Documentary Footage (6 betacam tapes). (Box 10)
    - Documentary Footage (7 betacam tapes). (Box 11)
    - "FLW; A Way of Life," notes. (Box-folder 3-17)
    - House and Exterior by Robert Gottlieb (1 VHS tape). (Box 9)
    - House and Exterior by Robert Gottlieb (1 VHS tape). (Box 10)
    - "Lois Gottlieb: Continuing the Legacy of Frank Lloyd Wright," Exhibition photographs, 1998. (Box 8)
    - "Lois Gottlieb: Continuing the Legacy of Frank Lloyd Wright," Exhibition material, 1998. (Box 8)
    - Plans of Mark Gottlieb (1 fuji tape). (Box 10)
    - Publications, title pages and table of contents, [1997]. (Box-folder 3-7)
    - Taliesen photo exhibit notes and correspondence. (Box-folder 3-14)
    - Transcripts of interview with Eva Soltes, undated (Box-folder 3-5)
    - Transcript of video interview with Indira Berndtson and Greg Williams, 1989. (Box-folder 3-4)
    - Transcript of video interview with Lois Gottlieb. (Box-folder 3-13)
    - Video project with Eva Soltes, notes, correspondence, and reference material. (Box-folder 3-15)
  - Photographs, 1995-2002, undated
    This subseries consists primarily of presentation photographs of various architectural design projects, as well as a photograph of a coffee table design and various portraits of Gottlieb.
    - Photograph, Coffee Table design, 2002. (Box-folder 3-12)
    - Photographs, Daniels House, Anacortes WA, 1999, 2002. (Box-folder 3-11)
    - Photographs, Daniels House, [Anacortes, WA], 2002. (Box 8)
    - Photographs, Gottlieb House, Fairfax Station, VA, 1996. (Box 8)
    - Photographs, Gottlieb House, Fairfax Station, VA, 1998-2002. (Box-folder 3-10)
    - Photographs, Lake House, WA, 1995. (Box-folder 3:9)
    - Photographs, various projects, undated (Box 8)
    - Portraits, undated (Box-folder 3-13)
  - Printed Material, 1953-2002, undated
    This subseries includes newspaper and magazine clippings about Gottlieb, a newsletter with an article by Gottlieb titled "The Balance Between Diversity and Specialization in American and Indian Education," product literature, announcements and other printed material related to an exhibit at Virginia Tech and to screenings of the documentary "Building a Dream," and other printed material collected by but not about Gottlieb.
    - Clippings about Gottlieb, 1953, undated (Box-folder 1-5)
    - Clippings about Gottlieb, 1960-1969, undated (Box-folder 1-6)
    - Clippings about Gottlieb, 1973-1979, 1998, undated (Box-folder 1-7)
    - Newsletter with article by Gottlieb, 1972. (Box-folder 1-8)
      (See also Subseries D. Environment and Design in Housing and Other Writings.)
    - Newspaper and magazine clippings of Gottlieb and her work, 1953-1974. (Oversize Map-case 13/Drawer 3/Folder 13)
    - Product literature, 1983. (Box-folder 1-9)
    - Various printed material, 1990, 2002. (Box-folder 1-11)
    - Various printed material related to lectures, exhibits, and documentary video, 1983, 1997-1998. (Box-folder 1-10)
      (See also Subseries F. Exhibits, Publications, and Video Production.)
  - Student Work, 1945-1950, undated
    This subseries includes drawings and class exercises created by Gottlieb during her time as an undergraduate at Stanford University from 1944 to 1947 and as a graduate student in the School of Design at Harvard University from 1949 to 1951.
    - Scientific Drawing, Stanford, Winter, 1945. (Box-folder 1-1)
      - Drawings, Harvard Projects, 1949-1950. (Oversize Map-case 13/Drawer 3/Folder 13)
        Includes 2 Frank Lloyd Wright designs - 6 drawings, House for Six Moon Hills - 5 drawings, Additions for Shady Hill Elementary - 5 drawings, Merritt Parkway food bar - 5 drawings, and Art Museum - 3 drawings.
        - Art Museum, undated
          - Architectural Drawings (3 sheets). (Oversize Map-case 13/Drawer 3/Folder 12)
        - Frank Lloyd Wright Designs.
          - Architectural Drawings (6 sheets). (Oversize Map-case 13/Drawer 3/Folder 12)
        - Merritt Parkway Food Bar, 1950.
          - Architectural Drawings (5 sheets). (Oversize Map-case 13/Drawer 3/Folder 12)
        - Shady Hill School Addition, 1949.
          - Architectural Drawings (5 sheets). (Oversize Map-case 13/Drawer 3/Folder 12)
        - Six Moon Hill Residence, 1949.
          - Architectural Drawings (5 sheets). (Oversize Map-case 13/Drawer 3/Folder 12)
    - Class exercises, Architecture 4b, Harvard, 1949. (Box-folder 1-3,4)
    - Drawings, Spring, 1947. (Box 8)
    - Memorandum, Harvard, 1949. (Box-folder 1-2)
    - Perspective Drawing, Stanford, Spring 1945. (Box-folder 1-1)
- Project Records, 1951-2002
  - Drawings, 1951-2002, undated
    This subseries consists of original drawings, including plans, elevations, sections, and details, of Gottlieb's designs for various residences. Drawings are arranged chronologically according to project.
    - Apartment 6 Remodel, San Francisco, CA, undated
      - Architectural Drawings (1 sheet). (Oversize Map-case 13/Drawer 3/Folder 11)
    - Beals Residence, Riverside, CA, 1968.
      - Architectural Drawings (12 sheets). (Oversize Map-case 13/Drawer 3/Folder 6)
    - Brenneisen Office, Hillsborough, CA, 1999.
      - Architectural Drawings (1 sheet). (Oversize Map-case 13/Drawer 3/Folder 11)
    - Brown Residence, Bel Aire, CA, 1952.
      - Architectural Drawings (6 sheets). (Oversize Map-case 13/Drawer 3/Folder 7)
    - Christman, Deltec Residence, unknown location, 2000.
      - Architectural Drawings (2 sheets). (Oversize Map-case 13/Drawer 3/Folder 11)
    - Conner Remodel, Seattle, WA, 1988.
      - Architectural Drawings (5 sheets). (Oversize Map-case 13/Drawer 3/Folder 1)
    - Curry Residence, unknown location, undated
      - Architectural Drawings (1 drawing). (Oversize Map-case 13/Drawer 3/Folder 11)
    - Dallman Addition, Reno, NV, 1982.
      - Architectural Drawings (2 sheets). (Oversize Map-case 13/Drawer 3/Folder 9)
    - Dallman Cabinets, unknown location, undated
      - Architectural Drawings (1 sheet). (Oversize Map-case 13/Drawer 3/Folder 11)
    - Daniels Remodel, Olympia, WA, undated
      - Architectural Drawings (2 sheets). (Oversize Map-case 13/Drawer 3/Folder 11)
    - Daniels Residence, Olympia, WA, undated
      - Architectural Drawings (5 sheets). (Oversize Map-case 13/Drawer 3/Folder 4)
    - Forster Stross House Addition, Harstine Island, WA, undated
      - Architectural Drawings (7 sheets). (Oversize Map-case 13/Drawer 3/Folder 9)
    - Galante Remodel, Carmel Valley, CA, 1988.
      - Architectural Drawings (6 sheets). (Oversize Map-case 13/Drawer 3/Folder 1)
    - Gottlieb Residence Remodel, Olympia, WA, 1973-1976.
      - Architectural Drawings (5 sheets). (Oversize Map-case 13/Drawer 3/Folder 5)
    - Gottlieb Residence, Riverside, CA, 1964.
      - Architectural Drawings (11 sheets). (Oversize Map-case 13/Drawer 3/Folder 6)
    - Gottlieb Residence, San Francisco, CA, 1955.
      - Architectural Drawings (14 sheets). (Oversize Map-case 13/Drawer 3/Folder 6)
    - Gottlieb Addition, San Francisco, CA, undated
      - Architectural Drawings (5 sheets). (Oversize Map-case 13/Drawer 3/Folder 9)
    - Grant Residence, Olympia, WA, 1981.
      - Architectural Drawings (15 sheets). (Oversize Map-case 13/Drawer 3/Folder 4)
    - Griffith Guest Residence, Olympia, WA, 1976.
      - Architectural Drawings (3 sheets). (Oversize Map-case 13/Drawer 3/Folder 5)
    - Gulden Residence, Olympia, WA, 1980.
      - Architectural Drawings (6 sheets). (Oversize Map-case 13/Drawer 3/Folder 9)
    - Hansen Residence, Seattle, WA, 1979.
      - Architectural Drawings (2 sheets). (Oversize Map-case 13/Drawer 3/Folder 5)
    - Harrah Energy Efficient Residence, Sedona, AZ, 1981.
      - Architectural Drawings (18 sheets). (Oversize Map-case 13/Drawer 3/Folder 4)
    - Harris Bathroom, unknown location, undated
      - Architectural Drawings (1 sheet). (Oversize Map-case 13/Drawer 3/Folder 11)
    - Haskell Remodels, Mill Valley, San Francisco, and location unknown, 1988-1989, undated
      - 1111 Chestnut Street, San Francisco, 1988.
        - Architectural Drawings (4 sheets). (Oversize Map-case 13/Drawer 3/Folder 11)
      - 280 Hazel Street Remodel, location unknown, 1989.
        - Architectural Drawings (3 sheets). (Oversize Map-case 13/Drawer 3/Folder 11)
      - 40 Wildomar St. Remodel, Mill Valley, CA, 1989.
        - Architectural Drawings (3 sheets). (Oversize Map-case 13/Drawer 3/Folder 11)
      - Location unknown, undated
        - Architectural Drawings (2 sheets). (Oversize Map-case 13/Drawer 3/Folder 9)
    - Heidar Residence, Lewis Co., WA, 1980.
      - Architectural Drawings (12 sheets). (Oversize Map-case 13/Drawer 3/Folder 3)
    - Hobe Remodel, San Mateo, CA, 1992.
      - Architectural Drawings (8 sheets). (Oversize Map-case 13/Drawer 3/Folder 1)
    - Holding Garden, San Francisco, CA, 1990.
      - Architectural Drawings (1 sheet). (Oversize Map-case 13/Drawer 3/Folder 11)
    - Jaco Residence, Riverside, CA, 1967.
      - Architectural Drawings (8 sheets). (Oversize Map-case 13/Drawer 3/Folder 7)
    - Jones Residence, Riverside, CA, 1967.
      - Architectural Drawings (8 sheets). (Oversize Map-case 13/Drawer 3/Folder 6)
    - Karen Gottlieb Remodel, Mill Valley and San Francisco, CA, 1990.
      - Architectural Drawings (7 sheets). (Oversize Map-case 13/Drawer 3/Folder 4)
    - Keading Residence, El Cerrito, CA, 1952.
      - Architectural Drawings (7 sheets). (Oversize Map-case 13/Drawer 3/Folder 7)
    - Knopp Remodel, Baltimore, MD, 1991.
      - Architectural Drawings (3 sheets). (Oversize Map-case 13/Drawer 3/Folder 1)
    - Lynn Garage and Guest Residence, Ketchum ID, 1990.
      - Architectural Drawings (7 sheets). (Oversize Map-case 13/Drawer 3/Folder 7)
    - Lynn Remodel, Ketchum, ID, 1987.
      - Architectural Drawings (1 sheet). (Oversize Map-case 13/Drawer 3/Folder 11)
    - Lynn Residence, Ketchum, ID, 1980.
      - Architectural Drawings (14 sheets). (Oversize Map-case 13/Drawer 3/Folder 3)
    - Mackey Residence, Riverside, CA, 1966.
      - Architectural Drawings (9 sheets). (Oversize Map-case 13/Drawer 3/Folder 7)
    - Mackey Residence, Riverside, CA, 1966.
      - Architectural Drawings (1 sheet). (Oversize Map-case 13/Drawer 3/Folder 7)
    - Maimoni Roof, Orinda, CA, 1988.
      - Architectural Drawings (1 sheet). (Oversize Map-case 13/Drawer 3/Folder 1)
    - Maloney Remodel, San Francisco, CA, 2001.
      - Architectural Drawings (2 sheets). (Oversize Map-case 13/Drawer 3/Folder 11)
    - Mark and Sharon Gottlieb Residence, Fairfax Station, VA, 2000.
      - Architectural Drawings (56 sheets). (Oversize Map-case 13/Drawer 3/Folder 10)
    - Mill Valley Residence, Mill Valley, CA, 1951.
      - Architectural Drawings (5 sheets). (Oversize Map-case 13/Drawer 3/Folder 7)
    - Mark and Sharon Gottlieb Residence, Fairfax Station, VA, 1993-2000.
      - Architectural Drawings (44 sheets). (Oversize Map-case 13/Drawer 3/Folder 2)
    - Park Residence, Ken Lake, WA, 1979.
      - Architectural Drawings (8 sheets). (Oversize Map-case 13/Drawer 3/Folder 3)
    - Park Residence, Ken Lake, WA, 1979.
      - Architectural Drawings (5 sheets). (Oversize Map-case 13/Drawer 3/Folder 5)
    - Pattison Residence, Riverside, CA, 1969.
      - Architectural Drawings (6 sheets). (Oversize Map-case 13/Drawer 3/Folder 6)
    - Popech Remodel, San Francisco, undated
      - Architectural Drawings (1 sheet). (Oversize Map-case 13/Drawer 3/Folder 11)
    - Robert Gottlieb Apartment, San Francisco, CA, 1984.
      - Architectural Drawings (14 sheets). (Oversize Map-case 13/Drawer 3/Folder 8)
    - Rice Remodel, Olympia, WA, undated
      - Architectural Drawings (1 sheet). (Oversize Map-case 13/Drawer 3/Folder 8)
    - Roe Summer Cottage, Olympia, WA, undated
      - Architectural Drawings (4 sheets). (Oversize Map-case 13/Drawer 3/Folder 1)
    - Roltner Cabinets and Furniture, San Francisco, CA, undated
      - Architectural Drawings (2 sheets). (Oversize Map-case 13/Drawer 3/Folder 9)
    - Shaw Cabinets, San Francisco, CA, 1982.
      - Architectural Drawings (1 sheet). (Oversize Map-case 13/Drawer 3/Folder 11)
    - Shaw Kitchen, San Francisco, CA, 1995.
      - Architectural Drawings (2 sheets). (Oversize Map-case 13/Drawer 3/Folder 1)
    - Skinner Residence, Olympia, WA, 1975.
      - Architectural Drawings (4 sheets). (Oversize Map-case 13/Drawer 3/Folder 5)
    - Skove Residence, Olympia, WA, 1979.
      - Architectural Drawings (14 sheets). (Oversize Map-case 13/Drawer 3/Folder 3)
    - Soltes Garden, unknown location, undated
      - Architectural Drawings (3 sheets). (Oversize Map-case 13/Drawer 3/Folder 11)
    - Stanbaugh Remodel, Fremont, CA, undated
      - Architectural Drawings (1 sheet). (Oversize Map-case 13/Drawer 3/Folder 11)
    - Storage Associates Addition, Annacortes, WA, 1999.
      - Architectural Drawings (9 sheets). (Oversize Map-case 13/Drawer 3/Folder 9)
    - Stross Summer Residence, Hartstein Island, WA, 1977.
      - Architectural Drawings (10 sheets). (Oversize Map-case 13/Drawer 3/Folder 5)
    - Unknown Title(s), unknown location, undated
      - Architectural Drawings (4 sheets). (Oversize Map-case 13/Drawer 3/Folder 11)
    - Val-Goeschen Residence, Iverness, CA, 1951.
      - Architectural Drawings (14 sheets). (Oversize Map-case 13/Drawer 3/Folder 7)
    - Vin Vanian Residence, Kharton, Sudan, 1972.
      - Architectural Drawings (6 sheets). (Oversize Map-case 13/Drawer 3/Folder 7)
    - Wheelis Residence, Hartstien Island, WA, 1978.
      - Architectural Drawings (7 sheets). (Oversize Map-case 13/Drawer 3/Folder 8)
    - Wieman Remodel, Olympia, WA, 1979.
      - Architectural Drawings (1 sheet). (Oversize Map-case 13/Drawer 3/Folder 11)
    - Wilhelmie Remodel, Rancho Sante Fe, CA, 1975.
      - Architectural Drawings (2 sheets). (Oversize Map-case 13/Drawer 3/Folder 5)
    - Wilhemy Weekend Residence, Ranch Sante Fe, CA, 1975.
      - Architectural Drawings (15 sheets). (Oversize Map-case 13/Drawer 3/Folder 10)
    - Wood Residence, Sea Ranch, CA, 1974.
      - Architectural Drawings (3 sheets). (Oversize Map-case 13/Drawer 3/Folder 5)
    - Wood Residence, Olympia, WA, 1974.
      - Architectural Drawings (3 sheets). (Oversize Map-case 13/Drawer 3/Folder 11)
    - Worden Addition, Riverside, CA, undated